Dirk Hornung, Ph.D.

City: Barcelona

Date of birth:October 5, 1991Place of birth:Fulda, GermanyMobile:+34 695460404E-mail:hello@drdirk.io

Website: drdirk.io



Dear Hays,

I am Dirk Hornung, a recently graduated PhD student at the institute of high energy physics of the autonomous university of Barcelona with 5+ years of experience in leading the technology in different Startups. Within my studies, I researched low-energy QCD and the determination of Standard Model parameters. In principle, I found intelligent ways to extract parameters of theoretical models out of experimental data.

Besides my studies, I am an entrepreneur. During the last year, I developed Smart Contracts in the Ethereum blockchain and connected them through REST APIs using Node Express for a legaltech. Before I developed a chatbot using artificial intelligence for a fintech. We connected our clients through Messenger to their bank accounts and analysed their banking information using Python. I am furthermore a Full-stack developer with lots of experience developing applications using React as frontend and AWS services as a backend.

I am very confident that I would be an excellent choice for any upcoming challenge!

Sincerely,

Dr Dirk Hornung

P.S. I am a native German, but also fluent in English, French and Spanish. Visit drdirk.io to get to know me better.

Professional Experience

May 2018 - Jan. 2019 **CYSAE**

CTO

Alda

Utility Token for Cuatre Casas, Certifying documents with the help of Ethereum, Enterprise Democracy on Chain

Tech: Solidty, Ethereum, Node, Express, React, Redux, GraphQL,

Prisma, NoSQL, Docker, AWS S3

www.cysae.com

Oct. 2017 - Apr. 2018

CTO & Co-Founder

Fintech Chatbot helping Millenials in Financial Education

Python, NLP, AWS Lambda, Dialogflow, Facebook API, React, Redux,

PostgreSQL, Serverless

Feb. 2017 - Sept. 2017 W

WeGoLoco CTO & Co-Founder

Matchin Tinder with the Local Commerce

Swift, iOS, AWS S3, NoSQL

Education

2015 - 2019 Ph.D., Theoretical Physics, Autonomous University of Barcelona (Spain)

Thesis: The QCD Strong Coupling from Hadronic Tau Decays

Supervisor: Dr. Matthias Jamin

Created a numerical C++ fitting routine from scretch.

2014 - 2015 M.Sc., Particle Physics, Autonomous University of Barcelona (Spain)

Thesis: 1-Loop Anomalous Dimensions of 4-Quark Operators

Supervisor: Dr. Matthias Jamin

2011 - 2014 B.Sc., Condensed Matter Physics, Goethe University Frankfurt (Germany)

Thesis: Band Structure Studies of Graphene and Modified Graphene Structure

Supervisor: Prof. Dr. Roser Valentí

Skills

Blockchain Ethereum, Solidty, Smart Contracts, Tokens economy, Decentralised Identity,

ICOs

Data Science Python, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Tensorflow, SVM, ANN, Mathematica

Frontend Javascript, React, React Native, Redux, Spring, CSS, HTML

Backend AWS, Node, Express, MySQL, Postgress, Node, DynamoDB, Serverless, Flask,

Zappa, Django

Prototyping Arduino, C++, Fusion 360, 3d Printing, CNC, Electronics

Marketing Photoshop, Illustrator, Final Cut Pro, SEO, SEM, Wordpress, PHP

Soft Leadership, Public Speaking, Motivating, Mentoring, Confidence, Energy

Languages

German: native English: proficient Spanish: proficient French: intermediate

Hungarian: basics